export const accordionItems = [
    { id: "currentAge", question: "Current Age", option1: "20 to 30", option2: "30 to 40", option3: "40 to 50" },
    { id: "desiredRetirementAge", question: "Desired Retirement Age", answer: "65" },
    { id: "currentSavingsInvestments", question: "Current Savings/Investments", answer: "$100000" },
    { id: "annualIncome", question: "Annual Income", answer: "$50000" },
    { id: "annualSavingsRate", question: "Annual Savings Rate", answer: "10%" },
    { id: "expectedRateOfReturn", question: "Expected Rate of Return on Investments", answer: "5%" },
    { id: "otherSourcesOfIncome", question: "Other Sources of Income in Retirement", answer: "Pension, Social Security" },
    { id: "debtsExpenses", question: "Debts and Expenses in Retirement", answer: "Mortgage, Utilities" },
    { id: "healthCareCoveragePlans", question: "Health Care Coverage Plans", answer: "Medicare, Private Insurance" },
    { id: "longTermCarePlans", question: "Long-Term Care Plans", answer: "Long-term care insurance" },
    { id: "spousesFinancialInfo", question: "Spouse's Financial Information (if applicable)", answer: "" },

  ];